hi welcome to class my name is Justin
attorney and I'm the digital analytics
evangelist at Google
one of the things i do is help people
understand the importance of making
digital analytics a central part of
their business
in this video I'll give you a brief
overview of what you can expect in this
course this self-paced course consists
of several components videos and text
lessons practice activities and of
course assessment
all of these materials will help you
learn about key concepts and tools to
become a better practitioner of digital
analytics and google analytics in
particular the class is divided into a
set of units each with a subset of
lessons and activities for you to
complete each lesson we'll have a short
video with the corresponding text lesson
to learn about the material following
each lesson you will complete an
activity that will help you practice
what you've learned during the course
you have the opportunity to connect with
a global community of participants the
community is a place where you can
discuss the activities get technical
assistance and get feedback on your work
you will also have the opportunity to
join google hangouts where you'll hear
from experts about the course material
and digital analytics
there will be a final assessment that
reviews all of the material covered in
the course to earn a certificate of
completion for the course you must
finish all lesson activities and pass
the final assessment with the score of
at least eighty percent including the
time it takes to watch the short videos
and complete the activities we expect
the course to take four to six hours but
this depends on your familiarity with
the content if you find yourself
spending a significant amount of time on
a particular activity or if you get
stuck
please use the resources on the site and
ask the community for help
finally be sure to check out the faq
page to get all of the important course
information and any updates
that's it we hope you enjoy the course
and happy learning